呃
Ugh!
一本交规
323 pages
323 页
of "Rules of the Road,"
而编者只字未提
and not once did they admit
左转进一堆车流里
that turning left into oncoming traffic
是很蠢的
is insane.
420 页的狼人和飞船的故事
420 pages of werewolves and spaceships,
而其中唯一我认真看的就是
and the only thing I'm really looking is that
我穿上特里斯坦的宇航服帅呆了
I think I could totally rock Tristan's space suit.
没错啊
Yeah...
等你看到穆尔斯战役那一段
just wait till they get to the Battle of Mirth.
也就是他遇见凯特拉那段
That's when he meets Kytra,
再后面的历险故事就引人入胜了
and that's when the adventure really kicks off.
你这科幻迷藏得够深啊
You undercover Sci-Fi geek.
你完全就读过这本书
You've totally read this book.
对  我其实全套都看了
Yeah, I've actually read them all.
我很喜欢这书  而且我必须承认
I love them. And I have to admit...
我其实看你去饰演特里斯坦是持观望态度的
I am a little on the fence about you playing Tristan myself.
好吧  其一  你怎敢这么说
Okay... one, how dare you.
其二  帮帮我吧
And two, help me.
得了吧  丽芙  你急个什么呢
Okay, Liv, why are you wigging out?
因为我真的很想要这个角色啊
Because I really want this role.
我知道我已经是个明星了
I mean, I know that I've been playing it cool,
但是参演的这部电影分量最大
but this is way bigger than my show
还能完全把我的演艺事业提升到一片崭新的空间
and it could send me into a completely new acting stratosphere.
但我却不知道怎么给脑残粉留下深刻的印象
I just have no idea how to impress these fanboys.
呃  好吧  我的确很想帮你
Okay, well, I would love to help you
但是  丽芙  我的驾照考试和你的
but, Liv, my driver's test is on the same day
签售会在同一天啊
as your autograph signing.
而我还不知道怎么
And I still have no idea
完成这个愚蠢的左转弯
how to make a stupid left-hand turn.
我有个疯狂的好主意啦
I have a twin-sane idea!
这周六  我就是你而你就是我
This Saturday, I'll be you and you be me.
- 等下  你指的是  - 姐妹身份对调
- Wait, you mean like... - A switch-a-Rooney.
我去摆平这帮脑残粉
I'll face your fanboys.
而你帮我把驾照拿到手
And I will take your driver's test.
太完美了
Perfect!
为什么你的床黏糊糊的
Why is this bed so squishy?
因为我坐在一摊比萨饼上啊
Because I am sitting on a pizza.
体谅一下半夜饿肚子的女孩吧
A girl gets hungry at 3:00 A.M.